Guide to the Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Performing Arts Photographs, 1914-present CTC.1966.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Productions, 1938-2011; I.; 1021.0 photographs
  - Paint Your Wagon, 1993; 1.0 photograph
    This file contains one photograph from Comtra Theatre's production of Paint Your Wagon. Appearing in the photo are actors Tom Orchard as Julio Valveros, Julie Unfer as Jennifer Rumson, and Frank Petroy as Ben Rumson. The play was performed September 16th through October 2nd, 1993.
  - Park Your Car in Harvard Yard, 1993; 1.0 photograph
    Park Your Car in Harvard Yard was presented by Mountain Playhouse from May 22-30, 1993. Photograph is of Judy Baird and David Garwood.
  - Peer Gynt, 1989; 2.0 photographs
    Peer Gynt was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from April 19-May6, 1989 at the Kresge Theatre. These photographs are of Yossi Yzraely (director) and Paul Kaup.
  - Perfect Wedding, 1998; 1.0 photograph
    Perfect Wedding was presented by Mountain Playhouse from August 18-30, 1998. Photograph is of cast members Nick Ruggeri, Wayne Schroder, Amy D. Forbes, and Janet Dickinson.
  - Peter Pan - Comtra Theatre, 1993; 1.0 photograph
    This file contains one photograph from Comtra Theatre's production of Peter Pan. Appearing in the photo are actors Bill Davis, Steve Mick, Tom Orchard, J.R. Vogel Jr., Adam Smith, Harold Graff, Leah Bulow as the Crocodile, and Frank Petroy as Capt. Hook. The play was performed January 21st through February 6th, 1993.
  - Peter Pan - Gargaro Productions, December 1994; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Gavan Pamer as Peter Pan. This Ken Gargaro production was performed from December 28, 1994 - January 8, 1995 at the Fulton Theatre.
  - Petrouchka, January 1975; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Dagmar Kessler and Alexander Filipov. This Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre production was performed from January 21 - 23 at Heinz Hall.
  - The Philadelphia Story, 1991; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of R. Bruce Elliott, Sean Cullen, Caitlen Larsen, and Michael Dean McCarty. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed from June 25 - July 7, 1991.
  - The Physicists, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Camille Hallstron and Michael Dowd. This University of Pittsburgh production was performed at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre.
  - A Piano Player with Sad Brown Eyes, 1982; 1.0 photograph
    Theis photograph shows cast members Leslie K. Armentrout, Cynthia Nelson, and Marti Donovan. The play, by Pittsburgh playwright F.J. Hartland, won the Carnegie Mellon University Bud Yorkin Playwright Award for Best Play of 1981. This local production also coincided with the play's Off-Broadway opening at the Ensemble Studio Theatre. This Allegheny Repertory Theatre production was performed at the Fine Line Cultural Center February 12th through March 6th, 1982.
  - Pinocchio, July 1978; 2.0 photographs
    This folder contains two photographs of Park Player's production of Pinocchio including Pamela Reynolds.
  - The Pirates of Penzance, 2002; 5.0 photographs
    The Pittsburgh Savoyards presented the Pirates of Penzance at The Andrew Carnegie Carnegie Free Library Music Hall in Carnegie, PA. The play was performed September 27th through October 13th, 2002. Actors Patrick Brannan, Melinda Fritz, James Critchfield, and Mary Beth Sederburg appear in the photos along with several other members of the cast. Photos by Greg Kornides.
  - Places Please, 1978-1979; 1.0 photograph
    This publicity photo shows Places Please cast members Marilyn O'Connell, Rob Marshall, Roberta Cunningham, David Tomkins, and Charles Altman. This Don Brockett production was performed at the Ben Gross Restaurant during the 1978-1979 season.
  - Play by Play, 1979; 2.0 photographs
    These two photographs show cast members of Play by Play. Included in the photos are Robert Koch, Bonnie Gilmore, Fred Donatelli, Rick Dolnack, and John Waterson. The Fine Line Theatre Company play was performed at the Lion Walk Performing Arts Center in Oakland from June 22nd through July 14, 1979.
  - Play It Again, Sam, 1994; 2.0 photographs
    Play It Again, Sam was presented by Mountain Playhouse from June 28 - July 10, 1994. Photographs are of Adam Bryant, David Garwood, Joanna Lott, Christine Laitta, and Caitlin Larsen.
  - Polygraph, 1996; 2.0 photographs
    This Quantum Theatre production was performed at the Purnell Theatre at Chatham College. The photos show actors Ferdinand Lewis and Karla Boos.
  - Portable Radio Circus, October 22, 1975; 2.0 photographs
    This folder contains two photographs of the Portable Radio Circus at Mr. B's Dinner Theatre in 1975.
  - Portrait, 1987; 1.0 photograph
    Portrait was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from November 4-17, 1987 at the Kresge Theatre. This photograph is of John Kozeluh and Jennifer Levison.
  - Prelude to a Kiss - Theatre Factory, 2001; 4.0 photographs
    Theatre Factory preformed Prelude to a Kiss February 2-17, 2001. Actors Elizabeth Matthews, Johnathan Surmaur, and Gus Melis appear in the photos.
  - Prelude to a Kiss - Open Stage Theatre, 2004; 6.0 photographs (on CD-R disc)
    Open Stage Theatre preformed Prelude to a Kiss December 3-18, 2004. Actors Joanna Lowe, Corey Rieger, Jack Goodstein, Erica Highberg, Ricardo Cooper, and Adam Kukic appear in the photos. Bill Hoenk is the photographer. The images and a file that contains photo descriptions along with other production information are stored on a CD-R disc.
  - Preparadise, Sorry Now, 1980; 1.0 photograph
    Preparadise, Sorry Now was presented by Theatre Express from May 15 - June 1, 1980. Photograph is of Randell Haynes and Janet Reed.
  - A Present for the Prince, 1982; 1.0 photograph
    A Present for the Prince was presented by South Park Conservatory Theatre in 1982. Photograph is of Palma Greenwood and Harry Bouvy.
  - The Price, 1983; 6.0 photographs
    The Price was presented by Pittsburgh Public Theater from May 12 - June 26, 1983. Photographs are Marilyn Rockafellow, Alan Mixon, William Hardy, and Harold Gary.
  - Prime Time, July 22-29, 1979; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of Park Player's production of Prime Time including Laurie Klatscher, Pamela G. Reynolds, Casey Childs, David M. Hugh, Ross Hamilton, Margaret McGrady, Catherine Roberts, Gela Jacobson, and Gary Jaketic.
  - The Prisoner of Second Avenue - Community College of Allegheny County, 1985; 2.0 photographs
    The Prisoner of Second Avenue was presented by the Community College of Allegheny County in the 1985 Summer Theatre season. Photographs are of Joe Clement and Rita Stetor.
  - The Prisoner of Second Avenue - White Barn Theatre, 1974; 2.0 photographs
    The Prisoner of Second Avenue was presented by the White Barn Theatre in June, 1974. Photographs are of Jeannie Wecsler and Richard McCarthy.
  - The Private Ear & the Public Eye, Oct. 5-29, 1977; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of the Holiday Inn Irwin's production of The Private Ear & the Public Eye including Ralph Kurtz, Jim Mikula, and Janey Potts.
  - Private Lives, July 1999; 4.0 photographs
    The Unseam'd Shakespeare Company presented Private Lives at The Lester Hamburg Theatre. The play was performed July 9-25, 1999. Actors Doug Mertz and Elena Alexandratos appear in the photos along with several other members of the cast.
  - Pump Boys and Dinettes, 1996; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Meghan Duffy, John DiPinto, and Mimi Bessette. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed as the opening performance for the 1996 season.
  - The Pursuit of Happiness, July 1995; 2.0 photographs
    Photograph is of Brian Robinson and Garrett Elise Long. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed from July 4 - 16, 1995.
  - Pvt. Wars, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    This photograph shows cast members of Pvt. Wars. Included in the photo are Robert Koch and Fred Donatelli. The Fine Line Theatre Company play was performed along with the play Lone Star at the Soho Theatre in Oakland May 29th through June 21st, 1981.
  - Quail Southwest, 1977; 1.0 photograph
    Quail Southwest was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from July 14-30, 1977 at the Kresge Theatre. This photograph is of M.B. Miller and Elisabeth Orion.
  - Rachinoff, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    Rachinoff was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from October 15-24, 1981 at the Kresge Theatre. This photograph is of Maxine Lapiduss and Rob Marshall.
  - Ragtime, November 2006; 3.0 photographs (on CD-R disc)
    These photographs are of Point Park University Conservatory of Performing Arts' production of Ragtime. The play was performed November 1-12, 2006. The images include actors Phillip Pineno, Sara Vize, Alyssa Gephart, Joshua Elijah Reese, and Kelsey Robinson.
  - The Rainmaker, 1.0 photograph
    Cast photograph from The Rainmaker at the South Park Theatre. Photograph shows Allan Nesvisky, John Imro, Lynne Franks, and Dale Irvin.
  - A Raisin in the Sun, 1999; 1.0 photograph
    A Raisin in the Sun was co-produced by City Theatre and Kuntu Repertory Theatre from September 10 - October 10, 1999. Photographs are of Javon Johnson as Joseph Asagai and Pascale Armand as Beneatha Younger. Photograph by Ric Evans.
  - Rape of Lucretia, 1977; 2.0 photographs
    The Rape of Lucretia was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from November 3 - 5, 1977. These photographs are of Judith Jenkins, Ulyises Espillat, Pamela Green, and Corine Salon.
  - Real Estate, March 1989; 1.0 photograph
    This photograph shows actors James Daly and David Bistarkey in Real Estate. The Community College of Allegheny County production was performed at the Boyce campus during March 9-18, 1989.
  - The Real Inspector Hound, 1984; 1.0 photograph
    The Real Inspector Hound was presented by the Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre from July 8 - August 6, 1983. Photograph is of Bob Wenzel.
  - The Real Thing, 1985; 2.0 photographs
    The Real Thing was presented by Pittsburgh Public Theater from September 24 - October 27, 1985. Photographs are of Mary Beth Fisher, Robert Moberly, Thomas A. Stewart, and Helena Ruoti.
  - Reckless, 1989-1990; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Helena Ruoti and Marion McCorry. This Pittsburgh Public Theatre production was performed from December 28, 1989 - February 4, 1990.
  - The Recluse, 1990; 1.0 photograph
    Cast photograph from The Recluse at the Laurel Highlands Regional Theatre from November 8 - December 2, 1990.
  - Red Herring, 2002; 1.0 photograph
    Red Herring was presented by Mountain Playhouse from June 18-30, 2002. Photograph is of cast members Susan J. Jacks, Nick Ruggeri, Tom Schaller, Janet Dickinson, Christopher Scoot Fuller, and Seana Simon.
  - The Red Shoes, 2007; 14.0 photographs (on CD-R disc)
    This file contains a CD-R disc with 14 images from Quantum Theatre's production of The Red Shoes. The play was performed February 8th - March 4th, 2007 at the Allegheny Unitarian Universalist Church. The images show actors Carolina Loyola-Garcia, John Marcinizyn, Alexi Morrissey, Erika Cuenca, Andy Place, Jennifer Tober, and Luke Savage. Photographs are by Mary Mervis.
  - Rege and Marge, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph from the Mattress Factory's production of Rege and Marge including Ann Beigel.
  - Robin Hood, August 13, 1977; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of the cast from the Dream Maker's production of Robin Hood.
  - The Rocky Horror Show, 1996; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of E. Mathews, Renata Carreon, and Jason Swauger. This Gargaro production was performed at Papa J's Mercato in 1996.
  - Round and Round the Garden, May 1986; 1.0 photograph
    This photograph is of actors JPaul Zielinski, Michael Safran, and Jeanne Rohach. The Orchard Performing Arts production was staged at the Apple Hill Playhouse May 14th-24th, 1986.
  - Rosencrantz and Guildenstern are Dead, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of cast members of the University of Pittsburgh Theatre's production of Rosencrantz and Guildenstern are Dead.
  - Rumors - Mountain Playhouse, September 1992; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Janet Dickinson, David A. Clark, Tim Sheahan, and Wendy Scharfman. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed from September 1 - 13, 1992.
  - Rumors - Red Barn Theatre, 2006; 1.0 photograph
    Rumors was presented by the Red Barn Theatre from September 22 - October 7, 2006. Photograph is of Christine Zuemie, Tom Bickert, Robert S. Hazen, David Cary, Paul Brenner, Tammy Herb, and Aaron Zimmerman.
  - Run Your Wife, 1999; 1.0 photograph
    Run Your Wife was presented by Mountain Playhouse from July 6-18, 1999. Photograph is of Kathi Gillmore, Christine Laitta, and Douglas Rees.
  - Run For Your Wife, 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of Greensburg Civic Theatre's production of Run For Your Wife including Craig Firment,Teresa Baughman, Rod Lively, and Scott Ludwick.
  - Runaways, 1983; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of the cast members for the 1983/1984 Point Park College Theatre Company production of Runaways at the Pittsburgh Playhouse Theatre Downstairs.
  - Sabrina Fair, 1979; 1.0 photograph
    Sabrina Fair was presented by the Robert Morris College Colonial Theater from July 26 - August 4, 1979. Photograph is of Pat Yost, Jeanne Gregg, and Sue Shannon.
  - Sagebrush and Sarsaparilla, 1975; 1.0 photograph
    Sagebrush and Sarsaparilla was presented by the Pittsburgh City Players from June 19 - July 19, 1975. Photograph is of Buster Flood.
  - Salvation Nell, 1983; 1.0 photograph
    Salvation Nell was presented by the New Group Theater from August 11-27, 1983. Photograph is of Kathryn Miller and Josephine Fisher.
  - Same Time, Next Year - East-West International Dinner Theatre, 1980; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of the East-West International Dinner Theatre's production of Same Time, Next Year including Marie Teets and Sam Mullen.
  - Same Time, Next Year - Mountain Playhouse, June 1996; 2.0 photographs
    Photograph is of Scott Wakefield and Mimi Bessette. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed from June 11 - 23, 1996.
  - Same Time, Next Year - Tonidale Dinner Theatre, 1.0 photograph
    This photograph shows Thom McLaughlin and Marti Ranii in the Tonidale Dinner Theatre's production of Same Time, Next Year. Photograph by Dennis E. Earney.
  - Same Time, Next Year - White Barn Theatre, 1980; 1.0 photograph
    Same Time, Next Year was presented by the White Barn Theatre from August 26 - September 13, 1980. Photograph is of Dan Maha and Barbara McCloy.
  - The School for Scandal, 2.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Benjamin Smith, David Novinski, KenYatta Rogers, and Lorien Clemens. This was a University of Pittsburgh Theatre production.
  - The School for Wives - Mountain Playhouse, September 1992; 2.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Lenny Steinline, Mark Baker, and Judy Baird. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed from September 6 - 27, 1992.
  - Seascape, 1983; 2.0 photographs
    Seascape was presented by the Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre from April 8 - May 15, 1983. Photographs are of Bob Stoll, Janet Robb, and Bill Mott.
  - The Second Time Around, 1993; 1.0 photograph
    The Second Time Around was presented by the South Park Conservatory Theatre from July 23 - August 8, 1993. Photograph is of Fred Lehman III, Lonnie Jantsch, and Gene Zizis.
  - The Secret Garden - Civic Light Opera, June 1995; 4.0 photographs
    This Civic Light Opera production was performed from June 13 - 18, 1995 at the Benedum Center. Photographs are of Jamie Cronin, Brandon Colwes, and Glenn Casale.
  - The Secret Garden - Mountain Playhouse, 1997; 1.0 photograph
    The Secret Garden was presented by Mountain Playhouse from August 5-17, 1997. Photograph is of Philip Wolfe, David Garwood, and Jenna Bull-Trombold.
  - See How They Run - Mountain Playhouse, 2001; 1.0 photograph
    See How They Run was presented by Mountain Playhouse from July 3-15, 2001. This photograph is of cast members including Matthew R. Marafino, Janet Dickinson, Neil A. Casey, Tom J. Schaller, Nick Ruggeri, Susan J. Jacks, Emily Elsener, Douglas Rees, and David Garwood.
  - See How They Run - South Park Conservatory Theatre, 1994; 1.0 photograph
    See How They Run was presented by the South Park Conservatory Theatre from July 22 - August 7, 1994. Photograph is of Keith Cecotti, Kathy Cecotti, and Sam Lane.
  - Send me No Flowers, Feb. 1978; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of Valley Players of Ligonier's production of Send me No Flowers including Jim Seabol and Marilyn Schmidt.
  - The Senior Circuit, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph shows actors Pat Reilly and Joe Reilly in St. Vincent's College Theatre's production of The Senior Circuit.
  - 1776 - Byham Theatre, March 1996; 3.0 photographs
    Photographs are of James Berry, Chuck Aber, Benjamin Moore, and Allan Pinsker. This Byham Theatre production was performed from March 6-16, 1996.
  - 1776 - Camelot Productions, 1976; 1.0 photograph
    1776 was presented by Camelot Productions from November 30 - December 23, 1976 at the Plaza Theatre. This photograph is of Jerry Comunale, Jr.
  - Seventy Scenes of Halloween, 1992; 1.0 photograph
    Seventy Scenes of Halloween was presented by City Theatre from March 31 - April 26, 1992. Photograph is of Lori Cadille and Douglas Rees.
  - She Loves Me, 1964; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Alfred Straumanis, Lindsay Holland, and Jeanne Gregg. This Pittsburgh Playhouse production was performed in 1964.
  - Sherlock Holmes, 1979; 2.0 photographs
    This folder contains two photographs of the Beverly Hills Playhouse production of Sherlock Holmes and the Curse of the Sign of Four. The first photograph is Kevin Hayes as Sherlock Holmes, and the second photograph is Winnie Flynn as Mary Mostan with Howard Moser as Dr. Stratson.
  - Shirley Valentine, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of actress Loretta Swit. This production was performed at the State Theatre in Uniontown, Pennsylvania.
  - The Shock of Recognition, 2.0 photographs
    This folder contains two photographs of the Holiday Inn's prodcution of The Shock of Recognition. The first photo includes producer Vic Kleeman, actor Fred Zezza, and playwright Jim Coates. The second photo includes Vic Kleeman as Mr Miller and Jim Coates as Mr. Barnstable.
  - The Show-Off, 1976; 5.0 photographs
    The Show-Off was presented by the Carnegie-Mellon Theatre Company from July 13 - 25, 1976 at the Kresge Theatre. These photographs are of cast members including Polly Rowles, Alice Elliot, Ed Rombola, Jewel Walker, John Ogden, Claudia Zahn, Eric Tavaris, Harry Ellerbe, and Steven Howard.
  - Showstoppers, 1979; 1.0 photograph
    Showstoppers was presented by the South Park Conservatory Theatre from August 24 - September 2, 1979. Photograph is of Richard Felnagle, Jackie Nicoll, and Carol Karl.
  - Side by Side by Sondheim - Carnegie Mellon University, 1986; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Risa Brainin, Julia Collins, Kathryn Burns Suber, Mark Lovett, and Gregory Steres. This Carnegie Mellon University Repertory Theatre production was performed from July 13 - August 2, 1986 at the Pittsburgh Public Theater.
  - Side by Side by Sondheim - Community College of Allegheny County, 1984; 1.0 photograph
    Side by Side by Sondheim was presented by the Community College of Allegheny County on November 29, 1984. National Broadway tour.
  - The Singular Life of Albert Nobbs, 1984; 1.0 photograph
    The Singular Life of Albert Nobbs was presented by the Community College of Allegheny College from March 13-17, 1984. Photograph is of Ruth Lesko and John Donnelly.
  - The Sisters Rosensweig, May 2004; 20.0 photographs
    This file contains 20 thumbnail images of scenes from The Sisters Rosensweig. The Jewish Theatre of Pittsburgh production played at the Katz Center for the Performing Arts at the Jewish Community Center of Greater Pittsburgh, May 6-23, 2004. The images are on two pages of photographic paper and are also stored on a CD-R disc.
  - Six Hearts in Three-Quarter Time, 1975; 2.0 photographs
    This Don Brockett production was performed at the Ben Gross Restaurant during the Fall of 1975. Photos include actors Marilyn O'Connell, Maggie Stewart, Mari Gardner, Chuck Aber, and Merle Stutzman.
  - Slow Dance on the Killing Ground, 1975; 1.0 photograph
    Slow Dance on the Killing Ground was presented by the Red Barn Theatre from June 13-29, 1975. Photograph is of Sarah Chodoff, Brooks MacKay, and Joe De Stio.
  - Snoopy, 2003; 1.0 photograph
    Snoopy was presented by Mountain Playhouse from July 1-20, 2003. Photograph is of Tom Schaller.
  - So What Else is Nude?, 1976; 1.0 photograph
    This Don Brockett production was performed at the Ben Gross Restaurant during the Fall of 1976. Photos include actors Mike Mader, Barry Catley, Chip Norwood, and Gene Harlowe.
  - Social Security, 1.0 photograph
    This file contains one photograph from Comtra Theatre's production of Social Security. Appearing in the photo are actors Liz Kline as Trudy Heyman and Judy Greene as Barbara Kahn. The play was performed in June and July of an unknown year.
  - Son of Arlecchino, 1977; 2.0 photographs
    Son of Arlecchino was presented by the Theatre Express from December 15-30, 1977. Photographs are of Susan Cash, James Edmondson, and Randell Haynes.
  - Song & Dance, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Michael Wilson and Lisa Prokop. This production was performed in the Theatre at Hartwood.
  - Song of Norway, 1984; 1.0 photograph
    Song of Norway was presented by the Civic Light Opera from July 24-19, 1984. Photograph is of unidentified cast members.
  - Sophisticated Ladies, 1983; 6.0 photographs
    Sophisticated Ladies was performed at the Stanley Theatre from May 24-29, 1983. Photographs are of cast members Duke Ellington, Dee Bridgewater, Gregg Burge, Jamie Rocco, Christina Saffran, Bruce Anthony Davis, Gregg Burge, Janet Hubert, and Ira Hawkins.
  - Sorry, Wrong Number, March 1997; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Susan Skosko. This Community College of Allegheny County production was performed from March 20 - 22, 1997 at the Boyce Campus Theatre.
  - South Pacific, 1981; 2.0 photographs
    South Pacific was presented by the Community College of Allegheny County from June 11-27, 1981. Photographs are of Joe Clement, Robert Bier, Trudi Gray, Jim McCrum, and Marga Laube.
  - The Spirit of Mercy, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    The Spirit of Mercy was presented by the Iron Clad Agreement in June, 1981. Photograph is of Lisa Cobetto and Doug Mertz.
  - Spring Awakening, 1996; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Thea Emily Nelson and Sarah Roberts. This Carnegie Mellon University production was performed from October 25 - November 2, 1996 at the College of Fine Arts.
  - Star Spangled Girl - Duquesne University, 1978; 1.0 photograph
    Star Spangled Girl was presented by Duquesne University the week of March 5, 1978. Photograph is of unidentified cast members.
  - Star Spangled Girl - Holiday Inn Irwin, April 1977; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of the Holiday Inn Irwin's production of Star Spangled Girl including David Shalonis and Jim Mikula.
  - Star Spangled Girl - McKeesport Little Theater, 1978; 1.0 photograph
    Star Spangled Girl was presented by the McKeesport Little Theater from September 16 - October 2, 1978. Photograph is of Ann Kinner, Randy Pingree, and Gerry Dalton.
  - Starting Here, Starting Now, 1987; 1.0 photograph
    This photograph shows Kim Cea, Ken Nelson-Suggs, and Pat Phillips in the Tonidale Dinner Theatre's production of Starting Here, Starting Now. It was performed in January and February, 1987.
  - Steel Magnolias, 1.0 photograph